## ANTHONY K. KELLEY

6403 Louise Ln. • Killeen, TX 76549 • Kelley.AnthonyK@gmail.com • (254) 226-7876

#### EXPERIENCED LOGISTICS MANAGER

Driven United States Army Veteran seeks a challenging and rewarding career with growth potential. Leveraging 10+ years of experience leading logistical teams, communicating productively with diverse audiences, and fast-paced, ever-changing environments. Looking to continue career with a company that values meticulousness, zeal and goal attainment. Trustworthiness, and confidentiality led to the awarding of an active Secret Security clearance.

## **OCCUPATIONAL SKILLS**

- Supply Management
- Supply Chain Management
- Operations Management
- Procurement

- Logistics Management
- Strategic Sourcing
- SAP /Equipment/Supply Ordering

# LEADERSHIP PROFILE

- Quantitative Research
- Process Improvement
- Purchasing
- Employee Evaluations

**Strengths:** Planned, and executed logistics support activities in fast-moving organizations with verifiable, highly successful results, created Standard Operating Procedures in Logistics/Command Supply Discipline/Financial Liability Investigations of Property Loss for six organizations

**Operations Management:** Demonstrated leadership in operations by creating support plans, logistical coordination, supply analysis, and personnel oversight. Overseen projects and inventory valued over \$275M;

**Proficiency:** Orchestrated and supervised the turn-in of over \$36M of excess/unneeded supplies and equipment; efforts returned needed funds back into the operating budget

#### **EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE**

## LOGISTICS MANAGER

- Managed the movement of property; oversaw six Organizations property valued over \$1.5 billion from 2012-2022
- Trained 72 employees in Logistics operations and in inspection program known as Command Supply Discipline Program (CSDP); SAP / WIN GUI
- Restored Government Purchasing Program as the primary Billing Official allowing up to \$10K a month, purchased per Unit up to seven units at \$70K
- Supplied logistical support for six organizations totaling over 2400 personnel
- Monitored data in SAP GUI on 36 units logistics elements, such as availability, maintainability, reliability, supply chain management, strategic sourcing or distribution, supplier management, or transportation
- Applied analytic methods or tools to understand, predict, or control logistics operations or processes
- Established training programs for 72 SAP users, promoting a better understanding of the system and increased efficiency in assigned employees
- Turned around 12 underperforming logistics departments/units within 3-4 months of arriving; increased performance metrics in all key areas
- Demonstrated quickly to assimilate new ideas, concepts, methods, environments, technologies and procedures
- Executed policies in six organizations that facilitated high levels of customer satisfaction in logistics operations
- Selected over nine senior peers to serve in supervisory logistic positions due to the proven skill to motivate employees, advanced logistics knowledge, and thrive in fast-paced, high-stress environments

### **ORGANIZATIONAL LEADERSHIP**

- Established positive workplace environments; trained 1000 personnel utilizing vignettes in Sexual Harassment and Assault Response Program (SHARP); instilling trust within the organization
- Rated in the top 10% of leaders on performance evaluations; outperforming those in and outside the career field due to proven leadership abilities and operational knowledge

- Supervised up to twelve employees at a time; administered daily work assignments, long and short-term career planning/development/guidance, and recommendations for advancement, employee recognition, and disciplinary actions
- Allowed junior supervisors to lead personnel while simultaneously supervising the entire operation, ensuring
  maximum efficiency of the organization while mentoring and nurturing growth of future leaders; resulting in 82%
  of promotions
- Educated and mentored supervisory skills at all levels over the past 20 years to ensure continuity and stability of military ethics and service

## (ORGANIZATIONAL LEADERSHIP Cont....)

- Counseled and mentored 72 junior supervisors, nine supervisors and employees alike, evaluating work and personal performance, and providing each employee with career enhancement capabilities
- Developed and employed warehouse safety and security programs and activities, which led to zero serious employee accidents while working in inherently dangerous environments
- Implemented two cross-training programs in assigned organizations that allowed employees to perform roles outside
  of the career field to meet labor demand during periods of staffing shortages
- Assessed the training needs of employees; designed, scheduled, arranged, and applied high-quality training programs
  to improve job skills on a weekly basis

#### **DECISION MAKING**

- Possessed systematic skills needed to quickly resolve common or complex problems earning 100% resolution
- Strengthened leadership competences to better enhance the productivity 5% and discipline of the workplace of 13 personnel
- Implemented direct and decisive leadership qualifications with particular strengths in planning, performance improvement, quality improvement, and productivity gain from 6 company's

#### WORK HISTORY

Logistics Manager, US Army, Fort Riley, KS	10/2019 - 07/2022
Logistics Manager, US Army, Fort Wainwright, AK	07/2017 - 10/2019
Supply Sergeant/Logistics Analyst, US Army, Fort Hood, TX	06/2013 - 07/2017
Logistics Manager, US Army, Fort Hood, TX	02/2012 - 06/2013

## **EDUCATION**

#### The CDL School, FT Hood, TX

Master Tractor-Trailer Driver Program / CDL-A 06/2022

## Grand Canyon University, Phoenix, AZ

Master of Science in Psychology with an Emphasis in Industrial and Organization Psychology 12/2021

### Texas A&M University, Killeen, TX

Bachelor of Science in Criminal Justice 08/2017

#### **TRAINING**

Senior Leaders Course | Sexual Harassment/Assault Response and Prevention (SHARP) Victim Advocate Equal Opportunity Leader | Senior Demonstrated Logistician Program | System Application and Products (SAP) Certification